gopaisa.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy

GoPaisa ("we", "our", "us") is an online service that help users ("you") to make better decision when it comes to buying the products online. We provide our users a go-to destination for smartphones which is replete with review texts and videos (shot by genuine users), expert advice, price comparison with other platforms as well as discussion panel to have an in-depth knowledge about the smartphones they wish to buy. Our website, mobile properties, and related applications are a part of the GoPaisa Netventures Private Limited.

If you are accessing our website and using our services, you acknowledge that you have read and understood our Privacy Policy. This also means that you are bound to take actions in accordance with this documented Privacy Policy of GoPaisa Netventures Private Limited. This Policy has been last updated on 02-24-2020. We may change the same as and when the situation arise. So, you are requested to periodically check the website as we might or might not provide notification for the same.

### An Overview

GoPaisa Netventures Private Limited is committed to provide its users an enriching and hassle-free internet experience. GoPaisa offers a vast repository of online stores and a variety of community services. GoPaisa obtains information of its users in two ways:  
(a) Information supplied by users  
(b) Information automatically tracked while navigating

By using GoPaisa or its services, you agree to the collection, storage, and usage of the personal information you provide (including changes thereto) for any of the services offered. However, your information will always stay safe and will not be misused in any manner whatsoever. Your continued use of our application implies that GoPaisa has your consent to send periodic communications regarding use of this site or any product or service purchased (by user) on our application. You may receive this communication through various channels such as emails, promotional SMS, push notifications, etc. These communications would be strictly in respect to our website or the products available on our website.

### Outlook

The Privacy Policy describes in detail our policy and practices regarding our numerous features such as reviews, expert advice, price comparison, discussions, etc. in detail as well as it informs you about your rights and responsibilities towards the same.

We understand that providing information online involves a great deal of trust on your part. We keep in mind the severity of the same and take every possible precaution to keep your information confidential and safe from any sort of misuse.

### Personal Information

To begin with, GoPaisa keeps your personal information safe and sound and makes sure that it isn’t misused in any manner whatsoever. To avail the services provided by GoPaisa you are required to provide certain information, such as your name, mobile number, email ID, residential address, etc. We also track your IP address for security purposes. The other details such as your age, sex and personal interests are discretionary in nature. However, all the information you provide, helps us to customize our search and we also use this information to improve our products, services, website content and navigation, which in turn makes your experience hassle-free. In addition to this, the other purpose for asking the email ID is to never let you miss any deal. When you provide your genuine email ID, we constantly keep you updated with the prevailing offers and deals on the various products so that you only end up purchasing smart. This information will also be helpful in keeping your “User Profile” updated.

Also, note that any of this information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is fabricated under the Right to Information Act, 2005. In such case, you are solely responsible for the transferring of information to different mediums and platforms

### Sensitive Information

At the time of processing your order or transacting for your chosen product or service, we may ask for your bank account details such as your bank account number and the IFSC Code. However, please be assured that this information will stay safe with our systems and shall not be shared or used by any other source. We also collect and store your mailing address in case you opt for cheque as your preferred payment medium to redeem your cashback.

### Security

We take required measures to protect your personal data from any external sources as well as restrict unnecessary internal disclosure or destruction. All the information gathered on GoPaisa is securely stored within the GoPaisa controlled database. This database is stored on the servers and is password protected. The access to this password is cautiously limited. However, it is a well-known fact no matter how regorious the security measures are, they are still not untraversable. In this high-paced evolving world it is almost next to impossible to guarantee anything. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone owing to the Internet access. If you happen to have any concern or query regarding our security measures, you may feel free to contact our support centre.

### Cookies

Cookies are nothing but a kind of electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique number as a User Identification (User Id) to understand user’s individual interests using our operating system. In other words, Cookies are basically small pieces of data which enclose information sent from a website and are stored by the user's browser on the hard drive. Be assured that this information is protected and can’t be accessed by any other website.

Cookies are helpful for us to track your purchases, your visits on different retailers/affiliated partners, exact time of your purchase. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. This help us figure out your preferred sites or products. With the help of these cookies we customize your search and brings you closer to your wishlist. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via website, application or Service through your computer/laptop/netbook or mobile/tablet/pad/handheld device etc.

### Account Information and Other Settings

Once you register yourself on GoPaisa website, you are entitled to receive periodic updates or notifications from us regarding various prevailing offers, coupons and other services of your interests. These updates will help you make the best use of your money and shop at the most reasonable prices. Also, these information will help you keep your user account updated, which in turn will help other users and experts to stay connected with you. The right information provided by you, will guide GoPaisa to create a community for all the tech-lovers.

However, we understand the fact that getting notifications every minute can prove to be a real pain. Henceforth, we let you prioritize your news feed and let you limit your communication as per your whims. We would also like to add here, that all the information which is critical to the cashback service can’t be opted out. At the same time, we make sure none of our emails are delivered in your spam folder.

Please take a note that GoPaisa, for security purpose, refrain its users from changing their name and email address. Nonetheless, you are free to update your rest of the information as and when required.

### Payment Information

If you make use of the products and services of the third party websites, the payment information shall only be collected by them, though if you transact through GoPaisa, you will be certainly eligible to get the prevailing offers and deals. We will gather general information including your credit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, authentication code, and billing address. We will surely transmit this information to the third party websites to complete the transaction. Please note that the third party website process your payment, not GoPaisa, unless otherwise specified. And, we understand that you agree to review and be bound by third party’s policies and procedures before making the final decision to purchase the product or service from that particular website.

Also, we might or might not offer our members the option to save information related to method and choice of payment on our website. If you save such payment details on GoPaisa, you will be able to add, delete or amend that information at any time through your “My Account” section.

### Location Information

When you use an application on any of your devices, we collect and use information about you in generally similar ways and for similar purposes as when you use the GoPaisa website. We might as well gather information about your location if you have enabled your device to send such information to applications via privacy settings on that device, or if you have uploaded photos tagged with location information. We may use the location information collected from your Device or photos to enhance your use of the Application by providing you with relevant content and contextual advertising.

### Advertisements

GoPaisa aims to provide you relevant and informative content on our sites to avoid any hassle you might have while transacting. Although to do this we may collect information about your product-related searches and other site-visiting activities, specifically about the features or the services you are looking for. As per the information provided to us, you come across various advertisements on our as well as other websites. For example, if you are visiting sites which is providing high-resolution camera phone, we would be customizing the searches for you and picking up the deals that suits your searches.

Please note that we not share your personal contact information (such as email address, username) with affiliated third party websites so that they can serve you with advertisements. There after you have the right to choose from those advertisements, in case you feel disturbed or annoyed by such advertisements you can unsubscribe from those mailers or marked them as irrelevant.
